Finding Aid of the WUWM Records, 1950-2014
University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee Libraries, Archives Department
- WUWM Records, 1950-2014, UWM Archival Collection 2; 9.4 cubic ft. (17 boxes, including 227 audio reels and 161 audio cassettes) 398 digital audio files (96.2 GB)
  - 10. WUWM Chancellor's Report, 2001-2014
    - Chancellor's Report, with Dave Edwards and Mike Lovell, July 2011, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 201107)
    - Chancellor's Report, with Dave Edwards and Mike Lovell, September 2011, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 201109)
    - Chancellor's Report, with Dave Edwards and Mike Lovell, October 2011, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 201110)
    - Chancellor's Report, with Dave Edwards and Mike Lovell, November 2011, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 201111)
    - Chancellor's Report, with Dave Edwards and Mike Lovell, December 2011, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 201112)
    - Chancellor's Report, with Dave Edwards and Mike Lovell, January 2012, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 201201)
    - Chancellor's Report, with Dave Edwards and Mike Lovell, February 2012, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 201202)
    - Chancellor's Report, with Dave Edwards and Mike Lovell, March 2012, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 201203)
    - Chancellor's Report, with Dave Edwards and Mike Lovell, April 2012, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 201204)
    - Chancellor's Report, with Dave Edwards and Mike Lovell, May 2012, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 201205)
    - Chancellor's Report, with Dave Edwards and Mike Lovell, June 2012, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 201206)
    - Chancellor's Report, with Dave Edwards and Mike Lovell, July 2012, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 201207)
    - Chancellor's Report, with Dave Edwards and Mike Lovell, August 2012, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 201208)
    - Chancellor's Report, with Dave Edwards and Mike Lovell, September 2012, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 201209)
    - Chancellor's Report, with Dave Edwards and Mike Lovell, October 2012, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 201210)
    - Chancellor's Report, with Dave Edwards and Mike Lovell, November 2012, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 201211)
    - Chancellor's Report, with Dave Edwards and Mike Lovell, December 2012, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 201212)
    - Chancellor's Report, with Dave Edwards and Mike Lovell, January 2013, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 201301)
    - Chancellor's Report, with Dave Edwards and Mike Lovell, February 2013, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 201302)
    - Chancellor's Report, with Dave Edwards and Mike Lovell, March 2013, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 201303)
    - Chancellor's Report, with Dave Edwards and Mike Lovell, April 2013, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 201304)
    - Chancellor's Report, with Dave Edwards and Mike Lovell, May 2013, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 201305)
    - Chancellor's Report, with Dave Edwards and Mike Lovell, June 2013, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 201306)
    - Chancellor's Report, with Dave Edwards and Mike Lovell, July 2013, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 201307)
    - Chancellor's Report, with Dave Edwards and Mike Lovell, August 2013, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 201308)
    - Chancellor's Report, with Dave Edwards and Mike Lovell, September 2013, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 201309)
    - Chancellor's Report, with Dave Edwards and Mike Lovell, October 2013, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 201310)
    - Chancellor's Report, with Dave Edwards and Mike Lovell, November 2013, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 201311)
    - Chancellor's Report, with Dave Edwards and Mike Lovell, December 2013, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 201312)
    - Chancellor's Report, with Dave Edwards and Mike Lovell, January 2014, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 201401)
    - Chancellor's Report, with Dave Edwards and Mike Lovell, February 2014, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 201402)
    - Chancellor's Report, with Dave Edwards and Mike Lovell, March 2014, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 201403)
- Miscellaneous Recordings, 1964-1965, Accession 2006-024; 0.4 cubic ft. (1 box); Materials from Doug Freshner, WUWM's first program director, including photo, print items, 4 audio reels (1964-1965) and audio cassette duplicates. Three reels (including recordings of James Farmer and Louis Armstrong) were added on 04/13/07 when donated in Accession 2006-056.
- Chancellor Baum Retirement Materials, 1979, Accession 2007-038; 0.1 cubic ft. (1 folder); Materials related to Chancellor Werner Baum's retirement news conference, April 1979. Includes an audio cassette of the event and a paper rundown.